let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does NFTs stand for?",
    answer: "Non-Fungible Tokens",
    options:[
      "Non-Fungible Tokens",
      "Not for Trade",
      "Non-Fungible Tickets",
      "None of the above",
    ]
    
},
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who can create NFTs?",
    answer : "Anyone on the internet",
    options:[
    "Big techs",
    "Government",
    "Anyone on the internet",
    "None of the above",
    
    ]
},
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "Some uses of NFTs is/are in",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options:[
    "Digital art",
    "Games",
    "Music",
    "All of the above",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "Do NFTs have the copyright of the digital files that are owned?",
    answer:"True",
    options:[
    "True",
    "False",
    "Undefined",
    "Undefined",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 5,
    question: "NFT data units are associated with _____ files alone.",
    answer: "Digital",
    option:[
    "Periodic",
    "Digital",
    "Both",
    "None of the above",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who first coined the term NFTs",
    answer: "Both",
    option:[
    "Kevin McCoy",
    "Anil Dash",
    "Both",
    "None of the above",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "In which year, NFTs were first minted",
    answer: "2014",
    option:[
    "2018",
    "2017",
    "2014",
    "2010",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "Why are NFTs bad for the environment?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options:[
    "The carbon emission is increasing day by day",
    "They consume a huge amount of electricity",
    "They add a huge amount of carbon to the environment",
    "All of the above",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "What does an NFT look like",
    answer: "Anything digital like art, music, painting and so on",
    options:[
    "Same as Bitcoin",
    "Anything digital like art, music, painting and so on",
    "Same as Etherum",
    "None of the above",
    ]

},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "How does NFT work",
    answer: "Using Blockchain",
    options:[
    "Using Blockchain",
    "Using Deep Web",
    "Using Non-digital objects",
    "None of the above",]

},
];